漫威出品
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     捍卫者联草
翻译     克里斯
校对     奶卫联盟
时间轴     念念
后期     拳拳和马律师的8T
总监     奶卫联盟
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
谢谢你们过来
Thank you so much for coming.
-很高兴再见到你们  -谢谢
- Good to see you again. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
-我们打烊了  -我们得关上灯
- We're closed. - We need to kill the lights.
-你怎么知道灯开着  -我说我们打烊了
- How do you even know they're on? - Hey, I said we're closed!
我们得找个藏身之处
We need to stay off the streets.
那就换个地方  我要叫警察了
Well, stay off them somewhere else. I'll call the police.
不行  你会让警察身处险境
You can't do that. You'd be putting the cops in danger.
-我先让你身处险境  -我不想解释了
- I'll put you in danger. - I'm done explaining this.
这是干吗
What are you doing?
她很强壮
She is very strong.
先生  这是为了保护你
Sir, this is for your protection.
我们得让这家店看起来关门了
We need this place to look closed.
确实关门了
It is closed!
我们不会伤害你的
We have no intention of hurting you.
-你会说中文  -当然了
- You speak Chinese? - You can trust us.
我还是听到霓虹灯的声音
I still hear neon.
谁会听见"霓虹灯的声音"
Who hears neon?
这位半瞎不瞎的律师
My blind-but-maybe-not lawyer.
什么  什么叫他瞎了
You're what? What do you mean he's blind?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以为他是来监视我的  现在我不确定了
I thought he was sent to spy on me, and now I'm not so sure.
-你觉得他是我们这边的  -什么这边
- You think he's on our side? - Our side of what?
-那个耍空手道的是谁  -丹尼·兰德
- Who's Karate Kid? - Danny Rand.
那个亿万富翁
Boy billionaire?
他脑子不太灵光
He's a little off in the head,
不过关键时刻  能打出漂亮的右勾拳
but he packs a mean right hook when it counts.
你也是
So do you.
你还好吗
You okay?
-现在吗  还是大体上  -都算
- Now, or in general? - Both.
我还活着  你呢
Well, I'm alive. You?
刚回到现实世界
Just getting back into the world.
-从哪儿  -监狱
- From where? - Prison.
我们过会儿再谈
Yeah, we'll... we'll talk about it later.
你怎么到这的
How'd you end up here?
-我在办一个案子  -是吗
- I'm working a case. - Yeah?
进展怎么样
How's that going for you so far?
后门安全  所有出口都锁上了
All right, back door is clear. Everything's locked.
我们暂时安全了
I think we're safe for now.
-我们就在这等着吗  -你有更好的计划吗
- So we're just gonna wait it out here? - You got a better plan?
有什么办法让我拿回围巾吗
Is there a plan where I get my scarf back?
等这一切结束就还给你
I just need it till this is over.
-你们认识对方  -对
- What, do you two know each other? - Yeah.
怎么认识的
How?
我们偶遇  喝醉  我朝他脑袋蹦了一枪
We met. We drank. I shot him in the head.
你怎么还戴着那玩意
Why are you still wearing that thing?
-这...  -好了  他说我们可以留下
- It's-- - Okay. He says we can stay.
-你跟他说了什么  -我只是亮出了黑卡
- What did you tell him? - Uh, I just gave him my black card,
答应他付半年的房租
agreed to pay the rent for the next six months.
-我是丹尼  -杰西卡
- Hey, I'm, uh... I'm Danny. - Jessica.
-你是...  -不  我不来这一套
- And, uh... you are? - No, I can't. I'm not doing this.
-哪一套  -不管刚才发生了什么
- Doing what? - Whatever happened back there,
我们是万不得已  我们活着逃出来了
we did what we had to. We got out alive.
我们越少了解彼此  这样越好
The less we know about each other, the better.
-事态已经太过头了  -好了
- This is... It's too much already. - Okay.
-别  -天啊
- Don't-- - Jesus.
-我有需要保护的人  -你不是一个人
- There are people I need to protect... - You're not the only one.
刚跟我们交手的组织很强大的
...and the organization we just fought are powerful.
-是吗  他们是谁  -他们自称为手和会
- Yeah, who are they? - They call themselves the Hand.
-那真正的名字呢  -不  他说得对
- What are they really called? - No, he's... he's right.
你之前遇到过他们
You crossed paths with them before?
-对  -什么时候
- Yeah. - When?
-这不重要  -不重要个屁
- It doesn't matter. - Bullshit it doesn't matter.
-我同意  -我们得想清楚下一步怎么办
- Yeah, I'm with her. - We need to figure out our next move.
不  没有下一步
No. There's no next move.
也没有"我们"  他们追杀我们  我们逃脱
And there is no "We." They came at us, we fought our way out.
这叫职业礼仪  就这样
Let's call it professional courtesy. End of story.
事情没那么简单
Look, it's not that simple.
-这些人很危险  -我也是
- These people, they're dangerous. - So am I.
谁快点告诉我手和会到底是怎么回事
Now, somebody tell me what I need to know about the Hand,
好让我快点上路
so I can be on my way.
那是什么
What is that?
那是...
Oh. Um, as, uh...
协议的一部分  他给我做了四人份的菜
as part of the deal, he made me order four of everything.
我们不是来吃饭的
We're not here to eat.
-那是猪肉吗  -不  是虾
- Uh, are those pork? - No, they're shrimp.
-这个人端的是猪肉  -太好了
- Oh. This guy's got pork. - Ah, great!
天啊  你真怪
God, you're weird.
手和会是个古老的犯罪组织
The Hand is an ancient criminal organization.
有多老
Define ancient.
-他们永远存在  -你想再尝一口吗
- They live forever. - You wanna try that again?
他们信奉狂热信仰
They live by a fanatical ideology,
并且每个成员都誓死保卫它
and every member is willing to die to protect it.
-所以他们是恐怖分子  -不
- So they're terrorists? - No.
恐怖分子想让全世界知道他们的行径
Terrorists want the world to know what they're doing.
而他们更隐秘  更邪恶
This is something more secret, more evil.
他们遍布全球
And they're global.
-他们具体做什么  -什么都做
- So what do they do? - Everything.
包括在哈莱姆招募年轻人
Including the recruitment of young men in Harlem?
显然
Apparently.
他们来纽约是有原因的  但我不知道是什么
They're in New York for a reason, but I don't know why.
-"狂热信仰"是什么意思  -真离谱
- What do you mean, "Fanatical ideology"? - Gonna sound crazy--
-他们想要什么  -永生
- What do they want? - Immortality.
他们想在全世界各个阶层掌控权利  树立威信
They want power and influence at every level across the world.
他们可能想要我
And I think they want me.
-为了你的钱  -不
- For your money? - No.
我是不朽铁拳
I'm the Immortal Iron Fist.
什么玩意
Come again?
昆仑的忠实守护者
Sworn protector of K'un-Lun.
你嗑什么了  锂盐吗
What are you on? Lithium?
那个拿剑的女人是谁
So, who was the woman with the swords?
我不确定  不过我在柬埔寨和她交过手
Look, I'm not sure, but I fought her in Cambodia.
对  她在我家门口出现过
Yeah, and she showed up at my doorstep.
她就是那个追杀你客户的人
She's the one that came after your client?
对  你认识她
Yeah. Why? Do you know her?
-不  -她肯定知道自己在做什么
- No. - Well, she sure knew what she was doing.
手和会把打手训练得冷酷无情
The Hand trains fighters to be merciless.
但不管她是谁  她跟他们不是一类人
But whoever she was, man, she was something else.
-抱歉  这就是个错误  我得走了  -去哪
- I'm sorry. This is a mistake. I gotta go. - Where?
我不能掺和进来
I can't be a part of this.
要我说  你已经掺和进来了
If you ask me, you already are.
我们得把一切摊开说
We need to put it all on the table.
我不认识你  我不欠你...
I don't know you. I don't owe you any...
我不信任你
I don't trust you.
你要不要把手从我肩膀上拿开
You wanna take your hand off my shoulder?
摘了你的面具
Take off the mask.
你不会喜欢事情的走向的
You're not gonna like where this is heading.
试试看
Try me.
天呐  律师  说句话
Oh, boy. Counselor, a word?
你想去哪
Where do you think you're going?
你得换个律师
You're gonna need another lawyer.
你为什么跟着我进大楼
Why did you follow me into the building?
琼斯小姐  丢掉我的名片
Ms. Jones, lose my card.
我也想
I wish I could.
听着  我走过这条路
Look, I've been down this road before.
-我知道我们要面对的是什么  -我知道你是谁
- I know what we're up against. - I know who you are.
不  你不知道  相信我
No, you don't. Trust me.
我知道  你是地狱厨房的恶魔
Yes, I do. You're the Devil of Hell's Kitchen.
或是恶魔小子
Or Devil Boy,
不管你喜欢怎么称呼自己
or whatever it is you like to be called.
不管你在暗示什么  我都不知道
Whatever you're insinuating, I don't have any clue.
我是个私家侦探  我会整理线索
I'm a PI. I put two and two together.
而且  你像个俄罗斯体操运动员一样
Besides, you leaping around the city
满城到处飞檐走壁也暴露了你
like a Russian gymnast didn't exactly help.
-你没有证据  -我有  被你砸碎了
- You don't have any proof. - I did. You smashed it.
我不是威胁你  这一切都太明显了
I'm not threatening you. I'm just stating the obvious.
他们看到你战斗  看到你遮着脸
They saw you fight. How you're hiding your face.
他们马上也能猜到了
They're two seconds away from figuring it out themselves.
-你想要什么  -没什么
- What do you want from me? - Nothing.
我也不想跟这个古老组织有什么关系
And I want zero to do with this ancient organization.
我只想解决我的案子
I just want to crack my case.
从你那么急于行动的样子来看
And judging by the way you sprung into action,
你也有同样的想法
I think you want the same thing.
你决定吧  默多克
Your call, Murdock.
我叫马修
My name is Matthew.
捍卫者联盟
第一季  第四集
如果可以  我会抹去一切你过去的印记
I'd erase all the marks of your past, if I could.
你的生命是新的了
Your life is new.
但很遗憾  你的身体不是
But sadly, your body is not.
我是这么死的吗
This is how I died?
别去想那个了
Don't worry about that.
现在重要的是  你如何活
All that matters now is how you live.
黑空
The Black Sky.
那是我的全部吗
This is all I am?
你说得好像那还不够
You say that like it's not enough.
不是的
It is.
我就是
I just...
你就是忍不住去想
You just can't help but wonder.
曾占据这具皮囊的女人
The woman who lived in this vessel,
她来到我们这里之前很迷茫
she was lost before she came to us.
她被害怕她本质的男人带上了歪路
She was led astray by men who were afraid of what she was,
他们害怕她的本事
of what she was capable of doing.
但命运是神奇的
But destiny is a curious thing,
因为这具皮囊  落在了她该在的地方
because this vessel landed right where it belongs.
到我们这里
With us.
到我这里
With me.
你是谁
Who are you?
黑空
The Black Sky.
我效力于手和会
I serve the Hand.
"我们一起  效力于生命本身"
"And together, we serve life itself."
你是我最后的希望
You are my last hope.
你见过死亡  孩子
You have seen death, my child.
你像我一样  征服了它
And like me, you have conquered it.
别忘了是谁带我们回来的
Don't forget who brought us back.
我不会忘的
I will not forget.
我听说他消失了
I heard he just disappeared.
并不是那样的
That's not exactly how it happened.
这没道理
It just doesn't make any sense.
什么意思  你是夜魔侠
What do you mean you're Daredevil?
说来话长  我也不想说
It's a long story. One I'd rather not tell.
更重要的是  我保守这个秘密
More importantly, it's a secret I keep
不仅是为了保护我自己
not just for the sake of protecting myself,
也是为了保护我所爱的人
but also for the people that I love.
-好  这我理解  -很好
- Okay. I get that. - Good.
-我不懂  你是盲人  -视觉也没那么了不起
- I don't. You're blind. - Yeah, well, sight is overrated.
听着  我们得想个计划
Look, guys, we need to come up with some kind of plan here.
唯一的计划就是如何摆脱这些人
The only plan is how do we get these people off our backs?
最好不会害我们落罪
Ideally, in a way that doesn't incriminate us.
落罪  你说什么呢
Incriminate us? What are you talking about?
我们都不是警察
None of us are on police payroll.
我们刚刚所做的是擅闯
What we did back there was trespassing,
重伤  和义警
aggravated assault, and vigilante bullshit.
各位  有一个警察我觉得值得信任
Guys, there's one cop I think we can trust.
我觉得我们该叫她来
I think we should bring her in.
不  你只会害她有危险
No. You'd be putting her in danger.
所有对抗手和会的人都会有危险
As will anyone who goes up against the Hand.
至于采取"合法"的手段
And as for doing this any "legal" way...
你看到我们尝试这个办法的后果了
Well, look, you saw what happened when we tried that.
-刚刚是这情况吗  -起初是的
- Is that what that was? - It started that way.
看啊  我还打了领带
Look, I even put on a tie.
我保证  这些人你打不过
I promise you, you cannot fight these people.
哪怕是用上你手的神迹
Not even with whatever it is your hand can do.
-是气  -才不是
- It's chi. - It's not.
我是说  正面跟他们对抗
What I'm saying is, going at them head on,
只会送命
that'll get you killed.
如果我们单独的话
Only if we do it alone.
不要
No.
听着  这些人夺走了我的一切
Look, these people took everything from me.
我无论如何都要扳倒他们
I'm gonna take them down, one way or another.
我只想帮助一个孩子  一个家庭
I wanted to help one kid. One family.
我自不量力的时候总会第一个承认
I'm the first to admit when I'm in over my head,
而这已经远超了我的标准
and this is way past my threshold.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
刀枪不入  盲眼忍者
Bulletproof. Blind ninja.
-不管你是什么  -真会说话
- Whatever it is you are. - Classy.
我试过单打独斗  但不行
I tried being a one-man army, and it failed.
但这
But this...
这似乎是一种天命
This feels like something else is at work here.
我们四个同时去打击一个
The four of us show up to fight a criminal organization
犯罪组织
at the same moment?
还得要多明显啊
How obvious does it have to be?
这
This...
-这不会是意外  -好吧
- This cannot be an accident. - Okay.
我知道你是好意  但我们不是你想的那样
I know you mean well, but we're not whatever you think we are.
好吗  我们是四个迥异的人
All right? We're four very different people,
虽然我们都想做好事
and while we might all have been trying to do some good,
我们得理智考虑该如何继续
we need to be rational about how we proceed.
开玩笑的吧
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
这算什么藏身处
This... is one shitty excuse for a hideout.
棍叟
Stick.
马特
Matty.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
要帮你们救纽约的人
The guy that's gonna help you save New York.
偷偷靠近一个拿刀的人可不好
It's a bad idea to sneak up on a man holding a knife.
谁说我是偷偷靠近了
Who says I'm sneaking?
亚洲黑熊
Ursus thibetanus.
月亮熊
The moon bear.
现在濒危了  但我在四国找到了这只
Endangered now, but I found this one in Shikoku.
我听说你去了日本
I heard you were in Japan.
你找人跟踪我了吗
Were you having me followed?
你有你的消遣  我有我的
You have your sport, I have mine.
我追踪了它十天
Ten days, I tracked him.
我们在森林里拳斗
We sparred in the forest.
它差点杀了我
He nearly killed me.
总是这样九死一生
They always nearly kill you.
否则也没意思
There's no fun in it otherwise.
你知道组织的立场
You know where the organization stands.
我们的资源已耗竭
Our resources are depleted.
你来不就为了这个  像训孩子似的训我
Is that why you came here? To scold me like a child?
不  但你该担心死亡的可能
No, but you should worry about the possibility of death.
就我所知  我们都该担心
From what I hear, we all should be worried.
我们快了
We're close now.
铁拳也回到了纽约
And the Iron Fist has returned to New York.
我听说你没能抓住他
I heard you were unable to secure him.
我们会抓到的
We will.
那就还差很多
Then we're not close enough.
你领导的问题一直在于
The problem with your leadership has always been
你不愿弄脏自己的手
your inability to get your hands dirty.
我们在一起那么久  我从未问过你的建议
In all our time together, I have never asked for your advice.
何必呢
And why would you?
你现在有黑空了
Now that you have the Black Sky by your side.
是啊
Yeah.
铁拳不是一个人
The Iron Fist was not alone.
真纯会不是被消灭了吗
Was the Chaste not extinguished?
他似乎找到了其他同盟  三个人
He seems to have found some allies. Three of them.
只有三个
Only three?
他们很特别
They were rather exceptional.
所以  你来找我
And so, you come to me.
我来找你
I come to you
因为我们一定要一起解决这事
because it's important that we take care of this together.
你告诉其他人了吗
Have you told the others?
高夫人和索旺达都准备好了  心甘情愿
Madame Gao and Sowande are ready and willing.
另一个呢
And the other one?
也在赶来
On his way.
我一直知道  我们有天会团聚
I always knew we'd reunite someday.
但我没想到会是在这么危急的情况下
I never thought the circumstances would be this dire.
家人不就是这样吗
That's what families do, isn't it?
那你的黑空呢
And what of your Black Sky?
你把我们最后的资源都花在了她身上
The thing you spent our final resources on.
她是你无法想象的强大
More powerful than you could ever imagine.
也就是说
Does this mean
我们忠诚的领袖也加入了战斗
our faithful leader herself will also join the fight?
一如既往  我做该做的
As always, I do what's necessary.
那  就像我们以前说的
Then, as we used to say...
"我们一起  效力于生命本身"
"Together, we serve life itself."
黑空
Black Sky.
如果你在战场上能杀死敌人
Perhaps you'd be more effective on the battlefield
而不是让他们逃跑
if you killed your enemies,
也许会更加有用
rather than letting them escape.
亚历山德拉坚持要我们把最后的资源用在你身上
Alexandra insisted we use the last of our resources on you.
手和会的终极武器
The ultimate weapon of the Hand.
但鉴于你最近的失利
But after your recent failure...
怎么说呢
well,
我忍不住自问  你究竟是不是件武器
I can't help but ask myself if you are a weapon at all.
继续问吧
Keep asking.
那人就一只手吗
Does that man have one hand?
-你怎么找到我们的  棍叟  -你认识这人
- How did you find us, Stick? - You know this guy?
-一言难尽  -那就多言几句
- It's complicated. - Then uncomplicate it.
-他是他们的人  是吧  -手和会吗
- He's one of them, aren't you? - The Hand?
不  还有一个组织
No. There's another organization.
我们自称为真纯会
We call ourselves the Chaste.
这些名字真要命
These names are killing me.
我们是手和会还未赢得战争的唯一原因
And we're the only reason the Hand hasn't already won the war.
我们追随昆仑的长老
We follow the elders of K'un- Lun...
和不朽铁拳
and the Immortal Iron Fist.
真纯会是我的军队
The Chaste is my army?
曾经是  他们都死了
Was. They're all dead now.
全都死了  除了我
Every one, except me.
怎么没人告诉过我
How come no one told me?
有些事我不知道
There are things I don't know.
你来做什么  棍叟
Why are you here, Stick?
因为他
Because this one,
不朽铁拳
the Immortal Iron Fist,
活武器和古城的守护者
living weapon and protector of the ancient city,
还是个大白痴
is still a thundering dumbass.
新规矩  小子  这种破玩意
New rules, kid. Shit like that...
会害死你
will get you killed.
我想打给科琳
I tried to call Colleen.
我告诉了她我在哪  她人呢
I told her where I was. Where is she?
比我们安全
Safer than we are.
小错误  个人羁绊
Small mistakes. Personal ties.
他们就会用这些毁灭你
These are what they'll use to end you.
你怎么回事  你的手怎么回事
What happened to you? What happened to your hand?
我为了解脱自己砍掉了
I cut it off to free myself.
我需要你的帮助
Now, I need your help.
-来了  -什么来了
- Yeah, here it comes. - Here what comes?
-他就这样  -你怎么认识他的
- This is what he does. - How do you know him again?
你见到我打斗了吧  我跟他学的
You saw me fighting? I learned it from him.
你是个盲眼律师  夜魔侠
You're a blind lawyer, you're Daredevil,
-还是真纯会的人  -不是
- and you're a member of the Chaste? - No.
我没加入过他的战争  棍叟  我们得谈谈
I never joined his war. Hey, Stick, you and I need to talk.
你想说什么  就当着我们的面说
Anything you gotta say, you say in front of us.
-这是我们之间的事  -我们都有危险
- This is between me and him. - Hey, we are all in danger.
我跟你不熟  凯奇先生  你看上去是个好人
I don't know you very well, Mr. Cage, you seem like a good guy,
所以相信我
so trust me when I tell you
这个老头跟神圣扯不上关系
that with this old man, nothing is sacred.
孩子  这次不是关于个人了
Kid, it's not just one of us this time.
是整座城市
It's the whole goddamn city we're talking about.
这是他们的生命  棍叟
We're talking about their lives, Stick.
是他们所爱的人的生命
We're talking about the lives of their loved ones.
-等等  什么  -整座城市经历的震颤
- Wait, um, what? - Those tremors that shook up the place,
跟将要发生的相比不值一提
they're nothing compared to what comes next.
手和会以前也干过这种事  庞贝  切尔诺贝利
The Hand's done it before. Pompeii, Chernobyl.
史书上把这些事称为灾难
Events the history books like to call catastrophes,
只不过是掩盖
just cover-ups.
因为纽约是下一个了
'Cause New York is next.
而唯一能阻止曼哈顿
And the only thing keeping Manhattan
变成一堆废墟灰烬的
from crumbling to a pile of dust...
就是你们四个
is the four of you.
好吧  我听够这些阴谋论了
All right, I am done with this tin-foil-hat shit.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我真的努力坚持了  各位
I tried to hang in, guys. I really did.
但不管他葫芦里卖的什么药  我都不买
But whatever this guy's selling, I ain't buying.
坐下  闭嘴
Sit down and shut up.
-杰西卡  -这是不行的
- Jessica. - It's not gonna work.
我知道这有些疯狂
I know parts of this sound crazy.
有些
Parts of it?
不考虑那些神秘  古老  阴谋论的玩意
Throw out all this mystical, ancient conspiracy stuff,
还剩一个不可争辩的事实
and you're still left with one hard fact.
有人会受伤
People are gonna get hurt.
-你不会  -重点不是我
- Not you. - This isn't about me.
你偶尔可以试试这个概念
That's a concept you might want to try on sometime.
饶了我吧
Give me a break.
这些你这么瞧不起的能力
These abilities that you have such contempt for...
它们现在或许能做好事
they might do some good right now.
这场战争  不管它是什么
This war, or whatever it is,
这不是我的事  我只想为我的客户讨个说法
this is not my problem. I just want to get answers for my client.
我也想要个说法
I want answers, too.
如果能帮我找到那个说法
And I'll play along with all this crazy stuff
我愿配合这些疯狂的事
if it helps me to find them.
我不知道
I don't know what it is
你为什么那么在乎其他人
that makes you care so much about other people,
但我不是这样的
but that's not me.
再见到你真的很高兴
It was good to see you.
等他们给你试紧身衣时叫上我
Let me know when they fit you for a costume.
杰西卡
Jessica.
你
Just...
要小心
be careful.
-那也是  -还有
- Yeah, you too. - And, um...
见到你我也很高兴
it was good seeing you.
嗯
Yeah.
她会回来吗
She coming back?
不  她走了
No, she left.
用你的能力感觉到的
Use your powers?
不  我见识过她这样了
No, I've just met her.
她怎么能不理解这多么重大
How can she not understand how big this is?
我不太了解她  但跟我一样  她有自己的生活
Well, I don't know her too well, but like me, she has a life.
不管是大是小  那是她的
No matter how big or small it is, it's still hers.
你经历了那么多  马特
After all you've been through, Matty,
我以为时候到了时  你的心胸会更开阔
I thought you'd be more open-minded when the time came.
请原谅我对于
Well, forgive me if I'm not excited
要再次迎战手和会并不激动  好吗
at the prospect of facing the Hand again. Yeah?
你是怎么卷进来的
How'd you get involved in the first place?
他是我见识过的  最有天分的战士之一
He's one of the most naturally skilled fighters I've ever known.
我见识到了
I saw.
我训练他去参加战争
Yeah, I trained him to fight a war.
他却决定穿身紧身衣
He decided to put on an outfit.
在小巷里阻止人打劫
Stop muggers in back alleys.
据我所知  你干得很不错
Well, from what I've heard, you're... you're doing a good job.
那是之前  他退休了
Past tense. He's retired.
知道吗  我们不要再谈这事了  好吗
You know what? We are not talking about this, all right?
随你
Suit yourself.
但我觉得你俩应该好好学习彼此
But I think you two have got a lot to learn from each other.
-当然了  -我不想再学习了  棍叟
- Of course. - I'm done taking lessons, Stick.
学习还不想放过你呢
Lessons ain't done with you.
这不是她的斗争
This isn't her fight.
迟早  每个人都会卷进来
Sooner or later, it's gonna be everybody's fight.
有我在就不会
Not if I can help it.
我也是
Me neither.
好吧  我们赶紧开始吧
All right. Let's just get this over with.
看来现在
Seems like now is the time
你该说出我们需要知道的一切了
for you to tell us everything we need to know.
谢谢
Thank you.
计划有变
Yes, there's been a change of plans.
我今晚有别的事
I have other business tonight.
好了  删除
All right. Delete.
奥黛丽·桑普森
艾比盖尔·金
安吉莉卡·弗莱切斯
阿莱斯塔·戴维斯
是同一个人
That's the same person.
怎么回事
What the hell?
没人知道是何时开始的
Nobody knows when it started.
几百年前  几千年前  无所谓
Centuries ago. Millennia. It doesn't matter.
很久以前  昆仑的长老聚集起来
But a long time ago, the elders of K'un- Lun gathered
研究如何汲取他们的气
to study how to harness their chi.
生命本身的能量
The energy of life itself.
他们想用它来进行治疗
They wanted to use it to heal.
但他们之中  有五个异端者
But there were five heretics among them,
他们有更黑暗的目的
people with darker intentions.
他们想要的不是治愈  而是永生
They didn't want to heal. They wanted immortality.
权力  永远不面对死亡
Power. To never face death.
一次次让自己重生
To regenerate themselves again and again.
长老把这视为离经叛道
The elders saw this as an aberration.
因此  就像从天堂坠落的路西法
And so, like Lucifer from heaven,
那五人永远被昆仑驱逐了
the five were banished from K'un- Lun forever.
他们成了手和会的五根手指
They became the five fingers of the Hand.
我在中城圈跟一个女人打了照面
I came face- to- face with a woman at Midland Circle.
她说她就是手和会
She said she was the Hand.
她这些年来用过很多名字
She's had a lot of names throughout the years.
在我这辈子  她叫亚历山德拉
In my lifetime, Alexandra.
她自一开始就领导他们
And she's led them since the beginning.
他们散开后
When they dispersed,
都回到了祖国
they all went back to their mother countries,
每根手指都统治自己的领域
each finger ruling over its own domain.
增长权势和影响
Growing in power and influence.
高夫人
Madame Gao?
她是一个
She's one.
她参与谋划了对我父母的谋杀
She helped set up my parents' murder.
她谋划过很多谋杀
She set up a lot of murders.
还有索旺达
Then there's Sowande,
非洲军阀  军火贩  什么都干
African warlord, gunrunner, you name it.
-我跟踪的那个  -别跟太近
- The one I followed. - Don't follow too closely.
只需几招
Couple of moves,
他就能放慢你的脉搏  直到你心脏停跳
he'll slow your pulse till your heart fails.
还有博徒
Then there's Bakuto.
他死了  至少我上次见他时是的
He's dead. At least the last time I saw him.
可算有点好消息了
Finally, some good news.
最后一个是谁
Who's the last one?
村上
Murakami.
在信背后指使他的人
The guy who pulled the strings behind Nobu.
或许是最神秘的一个  但当他现身
Maybe the most secretive, but when he comes out...
一个邪恶的家伙
an evil piece of shit.
我们一起就能应付
It's nothing we can't handle together.
这很好  棍叟  但你来做什么
That's great, Stick, but why are you here?
你要我们做什么
What are you expecting us to do about it?
别骗我  你撒谎时我看得出
Don't bullshit me. I know when you're lying.
或许你该别那么激动
Maybe you should just back off a bit.
这几分钟里
In the past few minutes,
他告诉我的信息远超出我在昆仑得知的
he's given me more information than I ever got from K'un- Lun.
那是因为他有所图
That's because he wants something.
因为他想要的会让所有我们在乎的人陷入险境
Because what he wants will put everyone we care about at risk.
-是啊  你说过了  -我还会继续说的
- Yeah, you've said that. - And I'll keep saying it.
我在这场战争中失去了很多东西  别把我当孩子
I've lost plenty in this war. Don't talk to me like I'm some kid!
-那就别像个孩子似的  -你说什么
- Don't act like some kid. - What did you just say?
-丹尼  冷静  -你去冷静吧  卢克
- Danny, calm down. - You calm down, Luke.
这些人不会给你第二次机会
You don't get second chances with these people, all right?
你一不小心  就会没命
If you're not careful, the next thing you know, you're dead.
或是更糟
Or worse,
你会抱着你在这世上最爱的人...
you're holding the people you love the most in the world and...
你会有幸看着那人死去
You get the privilege of watching them die.
好吧  或许城市有危险
All right, maybe this city is at stake.
或许这场仗很重要  我明白
Maybe this fight is important. I get that.
我只是说  想想看  余生一直想着
I'm just saying, imagine knowing for the rest of your life,
你的参与只让事情更糟了  天呐
you only made it worse by getting involved. Jesus.
几点了
What time is it?
很晚了  或很早了  看你的作息习惯了
Late. Or early. Depending on your life choices.
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
你还好吗
How you holding up?
还好  我...
Fine. I mean...
也就那样吧
as well as we can be.
你女儿呢
And your daughter?
她在睡觉
She's asleep.
-你喝醉了吗  -没有
- Are you drunk? - No.
那个...无所谓
I mean... it doesn't matter.
-你想进来吗  -不  我...
- You wanna come inside? - No, I just...
我只想说 你可能是对的
I just wanted to say, you might be right.
不管你丈夫卷入了什么事
So whatever your husband got into,
真是越来越奇怪
it just keeps getting weirder and weirder.
-你知道什么  -我不能说
- What do you know? - I can't say,
但我会想办法帮你们争取到保护
but I'm gonna work on getting you guys some protection.
-比如全天候监控  -为什么
- Like, around-the-clock surveillance. - Why?
-别问了  -不  我是说
- Please don't ask. - No, I just mean...
我以为你已经在做了
I thought you already did that.
-什么意思  -那辆车
- What do you mean? - The car.
从昨晚就在了  他说他是个警察
It's been there since last night. He said he was a cop.
他给你看警徽了吗
Did he show you a badge?
没有
No.
-待在这里  -等等  那车里是谁
- Stay here. - Wait. Who's in that car?
别靠近窗户
Stay away from the windows.
听到了吗  去  陪你女儿
Do you hear me? Go. Be with your daughter.
我去解决
I'll take care of this.
你怎么会还饿
How are you still hungry?
召唤我的气很费精力的
It takes a lot of energy to summon my chi.
怎么了  拜托  你都见识过了  两次了
What? Come on, you've seen it in action. Twice now.
我更喜欢它跟我并肩作战
I liked it better on my side of the fight
而不是打在我脸上
and not the side of my face.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me too.
别太习惯了
Don't get too used to it.
什么
What?
-我们是个好团队  -别用那个词
- We make quite a team. - Oh, let's not use that word.
什么词
What word?
听着  我并不想结交超级朋友
Look, I'm not looking for super friends.
是啊  你继续那么骗自己吧
Yeah, you keep on telling yourself that.
你去中城圈是有原因的
You came to Midland Circle for a reason.
我去是为了帮助哈莱姆  不是你
I came to help Harlem. Not you.
得了  我才不需要帮助
Come on. I didn't need help.
不是吧
You serious?
听着  我只是说  不论如何
Look, all I'm saying is, like it or not...
我们在走同一条路
we're walking the same path.
我们一起解决这件事  那条路就到头了
We fix this thing together. Then that path comes to an end.
最后一个
Last one?
我很高兴你找到了其他人
I'm glad you found others.
别假装这很正常
Don't act like this is normal.
别假装我不知道你究竟怎么回事
Don't act like I don't know what's really going on with you.
你也遭遇她了吧
You crossed paths with her, too?
谁
With who?
别骗我  艾丽卡
Don't bullshit me. Elektra.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
我了解你  孩子
I know you, son.
-她是你来的唯一原因  -她还活着  棍叟
- She's the only reason you're here. - She's alive, Stick.
不  不是的
No, she's not.
她已经不是她了
She's something else.
你没在他们面前提她
You didn't mention her in front of them.
你也没有
Neither did you.
看来她是我们的小秘密
Guess she's our little secret.
我听不到她的心跳
I couldn't hear her heartbeat.
那是因为我训练的女孩  你爱的女人
That's 'cause the girl I trained, the woman you loved...
已经不在了
she ain't there anymore.
-或许我们能帮她  -不  我们不能
- Maybe we can help her. - No, we can't.
他们复活她时  抹去了她的记忆
When they brought her back, they made her forget.
不
No.
她犹豫了
She hesitated.
她没杀我  她有机会的
She didn't kill me. She had... She had the chance.
别去寻找解释
Don't try to make sense of this.
因为不管你帮不帮忙  等时候到了
'Cause with you or without you, when the time comes...
艾丽卡·纳齐丝身体里的不管是什么东西
whatever is living inside the body of Elektra Natchios
都得死
is gonna have to die.
你也听到了吗
You hear what I hear?
外面有人
Someone's outside.
天呐  只有我不会空手道吗
Jesus, am I the only one left who doesn't know karate?
这个家庭已经经受了很多
This family has been through enough.
不管她丈夫做了什么  她什么都不知道
Whatever her husband did, she doesn't know anything.
她不是威胁  那孩子也不是
She's not a threat, and neither is the kid.
听懂了就点头
Nod if you understand me.
你会不再来打扰她们就点头
Now nod if you're gonna leave them alone.
我说清楚吧
Let me make this very clear.
他说了什么
What'd he say?
那是什么语言
What language is that?
我不是黑带  如果疼你说一声
I'm no black belt. You let me know when that hurts.
待在这里  锁上门
Stay back there. Lock the door.
你觉得是他们吗
You think it's them?
不好说
It's hard to tell.
他们怎么找到我们的
How'd they find us?
迟早的事
It was a matter of time.
里面是谁
Who's inside?
武器
Weapons.
几把枪  上满了膛
Couple of guns, fully loaded.
那个拿剑的女人呢
How about the woman with the swords?
我不知道  我分辨不出来
I don't know. I can't... I can't tell.
我的天
Well, I'll be goddamned.
这不会是我的第一选择
This wouldn't be my first choice,
但我就喜欢幸运饼干
but I am a sucker for fortune cookies.
我觉得我们应该
You know, I thought it would be a good idea
好好谈谈
if we all talked this over...
像成年人那样
like adults.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你让我意外  棍叟
You surprised me, Stick.
你老了却这么机智
You've become so resourceful in your old age.
那你老了变成了什么
What have you become in yours?
坚定
Determined.
兰德先生  很遗憾你如此突然地
Mr. Rand, I'm sorry your exit from our meeting
离开了我们的会面
was so abrupt.
你企图杀我们
You tried to kill us.
或许是想杀他们  但你不会
Them maybe. Not you.
我的组织一直很尊重
My organization has always had a great deal of respect
昆仑的保护者
for the protector of K'un-Lun.
你的尊重对我毫无意义
Your respect means nothing to me.
我唯一的目的就是扳倒你们
My only purpose is to take you down.
但你一次次没能实现
Something you've repeatedly failed to do.
或许该考虑其他选择了
Perhaps it's time to consider some alternatives.
没有其他选择
There are no alternatives.
亲爱的  选择总是有的
Darling, there are always alternatives.
所以生活才如此有趣
That's what makes life interesting.
少废话了  亚历山德拉
Cut the shit, Alexandra.
-你想要什么  -我一直想要的东西
- What do you want? - The same thing I've always wanted.
让光照向黑暗
To bring light into the dark.
让生命来到死亡之间
To bring life where there is death.
你口上说生命  却杀了那么多人
For all your talk of life, you sure kill a lot of people.
我们好像还没正式介绍过
I don't think we've been properly introduced.
那就别了
Let's keep it that way.
我看得出你们形成了一种纽带
I can see you've formed a kind of bond here.
这虽然能给你们些安慰
And while that might give you some comfort,
但我保证  那只是一时的
I promise you, it's temporary.
他们会让你失望
They will disappoint you.
他们现在还没呢
They haven't yet.
他们不会让你更加强大
They will not make you stronger.
容我给你一句建议
And if I might give you some advice,
你的羁绊越多
the more connections you have,
你越容易被打倒
the easier it will be to break you.
你想对他做什么
What do you want to do with him?
这我不能说
Well, I can't disclose that.
但我可以说我愿为他做什么
But I'll tell you what I'm willing to do for him.
我会汇集我组织的一切资源
I'll assemble all the resources my organization has to offer.
你记得上次
You remember the last time
手和会的所有手指聚集在一起的时候吧  棍叟
all the fingers of the Hand came together, don't you, Stick?
一次大筛选
A goddamn culling.
纽约是个人口如此密集的地方
And New York is so densely populated.
你在说什么
What are you talking about doing?
想想看如果你跟我走  能救下多少生命
Think of how many lives you can save if you just come with me.
你想要什么
What do you want?
孩子  想都别想
Kid, don't even think about it.
我只想要答案
I just want an answer.
我甚至可以放走他们
I might even let them go free.
你跟她走
You walk with her...
我就亲手干掉你
and I'll take you out myself.
我哪都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
兰德先生
Mr. Rand...
你得想清楚
you need to think this through.
你得走了
And you need to leave.
马上
Now.
他们跟你一样  老头子
They're just like you, old man.
他们唯一会说的语言  就是暴力
The only language they speak is violence.
来吧  我的孩子
Go on, my child.
效力生命本身
Serve life itself.
有谁想我了吗
Who missed me?